brand24.com 2019-12-03

# Brand24

### Privacy PolicyBrand24 Global Inc.

###### _Last modified: May 24, 2018_

Brand24 Global Inc., a Delaware corporation (“ **Brand24** ”) provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of:

  * our website at [www.brand24.com](http://www.brand24.com/) and other websites where this Privacy Policy is posted (collectively, the “ **Site** ”); and
  * the services, software, applications, plug-ins, components, functionality, or programs provided or offered now or in the future (collectively, the “ **Services** ”) on the Site or through our mobile applications (each, an “ **App** ”). 

Throughout this Privacy Policy, “ **you** ” or “ **your** ” shall refer to any person or entity using the Site, Services, or App, and “ **we** ,” “ **our** ” or “ **us** ” will refer collectively to Brand24, Brand24 SA, and other corporate affiliates.  For purposes of applicable privacy laws and regulations, Brand24 is the “Controller” and Brand24 and other corporate affiliates are “Processors” and Brand24 S.A. is Brand24’s designated represented in the European Union. 

You can access most of our Site and our Apps without having to provide any information about yourself.  But we do automatically collect some information through the use of Tags (e.g., cookies, pixel tags, web beacons, etc.), so please review the section of this Privacy Policy below to see how we collect and use such information.  Additionally, if you don’t provide certain information, you might not be able to access all of the Site and you won’t be able to communicate with us or purchase any of the Services that we offer.

Please note that by using the Site or Services or by downloading any Apps, you agree to the terms in this Privacy Policy.  If you do not agree to the terms in this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site or Services, nor download any Apps. 

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time.  If we change this Privacy Policy, we will update the “Last modified” date above and provide a notice about the update on any Apps. Continued use of the Site, Services, or any Apps after the effective date of a Privacy Policy change will constitute your acceptance of those changes. 

#### **CONSENT TO COLLECTION, USE, SHARING, AND TRANSFER OF INFORMATION**

By using this Site, any Apps, or our Services, you expressly consent to:

  * the collection, use, and sharing of your information as described in this Privacy Policy; and 
  * the transfer, maintenance, and processing of your information in the United States.

Our servers are located in the United States of America and Poland. If you are not a U.S. citizen or if you are accessing the Site, any Apps, or our Services from outside the United States, please be advised that through your use of the Site, Apps, or Services, you are consenting to the transfer of your personal information to the United States, which might not have protections that meet applicable requirements in the country in which you are a citizen or are located. 

We have put in place commercially reasonable physical, electronic, and organizational procedures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure, or destruction of your information.  For example, we use secure socket layer technology (SSL), which is designed to encrypt the transmission of information shared between your browser and our Site or Apps, and the information we collect is stored and transmitted using 128-bit encryption.  We also require our affiliates and third parties outside of the European Union to agree to standard contractual data protection clauses that have been approved by the European Commission before we transfer your information to them.  And affiliates and third parties that receive your information may only use or share it only in accordance with (i) written data processing agreements that impose privacy and data security obligations, and (ii) our instruction.

Our collection, use, sharing, and transfer of your information will remain subject to this Privacy Policy, but we cannot guarantee your information will be absolutely secure or that unauthorized persons will not access or use your personal information for improper purposes. 

In the event of a breach of security affecting the personal information that you have provided to us, or the personal information that we have collected, we will take remedial actions as required by applicable laws, which might include providing you notice of such breach.  You agree that we may send you such notices via the Site or Apps, or by phone, email, or mail.

#### **INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

**_Information you provide._**   When you sign up for the Services, download any Apps, or purchase any products using the Services Site, we may collect:

  * various personal information, including your name, mailing address, email address, phone number, username, password, demographic information (such as your age, gender, occupation), and third party social media profile information; and 
  * other information you directly provide on our Site, using any Apps, or using our Services. 

Some of this information will be retrieved and saved on our systems and may include a user token or other persistent identifier. 

**_Direct communications_.**  When you send email, post information on the Site, or communicate directly with us by some other method, we may retain those communications in order to process inquiries about you, respond to requests about you, and provide Services that you request of us.  We may use your email address, phone number, or other means of communication that you authorize to communicate with you about our Services.

**_Information we get from others._**   If you (i) purchase or otherwise utilize our Services, or (ii) register or log into the Site or any App using a third party authenticator login (such as Facebook), you authorize us to access and collect certain information from third parties such as your public profile, email address, gender, birthday, education history, work history, interests, current city, photos, videos, personal description, friend list, ratings and reviews, posts, biographical information, interests, “likes,” tweets, re-tweets, social media mentions and followers, and other information available in the public domain or available from the third-party authenticator if you use one to login or to register. This information may be obtained using different algorithms, through social media APIs, or other sources, and may be combined with information you provide directly to us.

**_Information Automatically Collected; Cookies; Tags._**   When you use the Site, any Apps, or our Services, we may collect information about you and your computer or device, including through the use of both session and persistent “cookies,” “pixel tags,” or “web beacons” (collectively, “ **Tags** ”).  “Cookies” are small data files stored on your hard drive, and “pixel tags” or “web beacons” are small graphic files placed on a website or within the body of an email for the purpose of tracking activity on websites, or when emails are opened or accessed.  A “session” Tag will not collect information once you close the program used to access the Tag (e.g., a web browser), and a persistent Tag will collect information until its deleted.

The type of information we automatically collect when you use our Site, any Apps, or Services includes the IP (Internet Protocol) address of your computer or device; information about other Tags on your computer or device; the website you visited before visiting our Site; pages you viewed on our Site; how long you spent accessing each page; how long you used an App; times and dates that you accessed the Site, used an Apps, or used our Services; your computer or device type; computer or device operating system type; browser type; browser language; and other information about how you used or accessed the Site, any Apps, or our Services.

You can typically remove and reject Tags with your browser or media-device settings. Many browsers and media-devices are set to accept Tags unless you change your settings. If you remove or reject our Tags, it could affect how our Site or App works for you.

We also use Google Analytics to understand how the site is being used. Google Analytics uses permanent cookies on your web browser to identify you as a unique user.  Please see Google’s privacy policy for more information on how such data is collected and shared by Google.

#### **HOW WE USE AND SHARE INFORMATION**

**_Routine Maintenance and Operations; Services.  _** We use information you provide and information that we collect to:

  * operate, maintain, and improve the Services, Site, and Apps
  * perform the Services
  * provide information you request or respond to communications from you
  * improve and customize your experience, including remembering information so you will not have to reenter it and provide access to your data
  * contact you regarding Services changes, system maintenance and outage issues, account issues, or otherwise troubleshoot problems.

**_Communication with purchasers.   _**If you purchase any of our Services, you agree that we may communicate with you about the Services by phone, email, or mail.

**_Affiliates and third-party service providers._**   We will disclose information to affiliates or service providers that assist with the Services, the Site, or Apps.  For example, if you order our products, we may work with a payment processing company and with logistic providers to process your payment and to process, package, ship, and deliver material related to the Services. All payments by credit card are processed by Brand24; all payments by bank wire are processed by Brand24 S.A.  We do not permit these providers to use your information other than as necessary to provide the services to us. 

**_Marketing Communications._**   If you “opt-in” to receive our newsletter or other marketing or promotional communications, we may use your information to email you about promotions, upcoming events, and other news about products and services offered by us and our selected partners.  Our emails will tell you how to “opt-out.”  If you opt out, we may still send you non-marketing emails, including emails about our software usage, purchase confirmations, invoices, technical notices, security alerts, notifications from our sofware and support and administrative messages.

Additionally, if you “opt-in” to receive advertisements from third parties, we may disclose your information, including location data, to third parties for marketing purposes such as targeted advertisements and information our advertising partners believe may be of relevance and interest to you.  You can opt-out of our collection of location data by rejecting our request to collect such data or by contacting us using our contact information below.

If you “opt-in” to marketing communications, such marketing communications help us continue providing our Services, including our products, at our superb prices.  But your privacy is important to us, so you have the right to prevent disclosure of your personal information for marketing purposes by either electing not to “opt-in” to marketing communications or by “opting out” at any time after you “opt-in.”

**_Other disclosures._**   We may use or disclose your information if we have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to:

  * satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or other governmental or law enforcement request; 
  * enforce our Terms of Use, including investigation of potential violations; 
  * detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; or 
  * protect against or mitigate harm to the rights, property or safety of Brand24, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

**_Aggregate and non-personally identifiable information._**   Brand24 may use non-identifiable anonymous data and combine it with other anonymous data to create what is referred to as “Aggregate Data” that may be disclosed to third parties. Aggregate Data is information that describes the habits, usage patterns and/or demographics of users as a group but does not reveal the identity of particular users.  For example, Aggregate Data may provide information on features of the Services that are most used or visited.  Aggregate Data may be used to determine such things as user demographics and usage patterns for our Site, Services, and Apps. 

Brand24 may use Aggregate Data within Brand24 to understand the needs of the Brand24 community of users and determine what kinds of programs and services we can offer, including improvements and new offerings. We may also share Aggregate Data with third parties. 

**_Corporate events._**   If we become involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of our assets, your information may be included in the assets sold or transferred to the acquirer.  You agree that we may transfer or assign the information we have collected about you in connection with any such event.

**_With permission._**   We may share your information for reasons not described in this Privacy Policy only with your permission.

#### **FINANCIAL TRANSACTIONS**

We use third party payment processors, including Recurly and Stripe, to process financial payments for certain services. When you make payments to us or obtain certain products or services, we may transfer certain information (including personally identifying information) to these payment processors for the sole purpose of facilitating the payment transaction, including your name, address, and credit card information.

#### RETENTION, ACCESS, REVISION, AND DELITION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

You may access, update, change, correct, and delete most of your personal information through the Site or Apps.  Additionally, by contacting us using the “Contact Us” information below, you may request:

  * a copy of information that we have collected about you;
  * that we correct inaccurate information that we have collected about you;
  * that we delete the information we have collected about you; or
  * certain limitations on or object to our collection, use, sharing, or processing of your information.

We will promptly take appropriate action in response to your request, but we will retain information about you for as long as (i) you use our Services or maintain an active account, (ii) we are legally required to do so, or (iii) we have a legitimate and legal reason for doing so.

Specifically, billing information is retained for 4 years for purposes of accounting and tax laws, and information about legal transactions is retained for 10 years to enable us to review any ongoing legal obligations, to resolve disputes, and to enforce agreements.  And we will retain your information for marketing communications until you “opt-out” of such communications or request that we delete all the information that we have collected about you.

#### THIRD-PARTY SITES

**_Social media sites._** _  _We may have pages or other presence on various social networking sites or services, such as Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, and others.  Any information you post or provide through such sites and services will be subject to the policies of those sites and services, though we will collect, use, and share such information only in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**_Links to third-party sites._** _  _The Services may provide links to third-party websites for your convenience and information.  If you use such links, you will leave the Site.  We do not control such linked third-party sites or any third party’s privacy practices.  We do not endorse or make any representations about third parties or third-party websites.  The information you choose to give to third parties is not covered by our Privacy Policy.  We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any third party if you access third party site using a link on our Site or on any Apps.

#### Information of Children

The Services is not intended for use by minors under the age of 13, unless through an Authorized Individual Representative.  If we learn that a child under the age of 13 has provided us with personal information without verifiable parental consent, we will promptly take reasonable and appropriate actions to remove such user and delete any personal information from our servers.

#### **Contact us**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding this Privacy Policy, or if you want to correct or delete information that we have collected about you, please contact us at: [help@brand24.pl](mailto:help@brand24.pl) or +1 (718) 618-4483

#### **Complaints**

If you believe we are processing your personal data in violation of this Privacy Policy or in violation of the law, you can contact the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO) in the European Union or the Federal Trade Commission (FTC) or your state’s attorney general in the United States.
